Today actually the insurance sector is in flavour,
I am actually seeing two strokes
but just finding out from that is
ICICI Lombard, ICICI
Lombard, ICICI LG,
ICICI Jal, the
rate is running at 1258, right now in the future,
this means complete, if you
see the monthly chart, then its high was made of 1672
in September 21 and from there
it was continuously in the down trend and it has
reversed by making a low of 117 and now
such a good technical setup has been made that
it is also a very good follower stock and even now
for the short term, technically it is
very well place, talk is going on right now,
1257, 1257 and I am
seeing a minimum target of 1300 nearby and after going above that,
we can also see a target of 1500 nearby and
for this we will have to put a stop loss of
110, so by putting this stop loss, definitely we can have
This stock is for short term, medium
term and long term because
it is showing very good technical condition right now.
From the insurance sector, I have given the rating
of ICICI Lombard.